http://elpla.com/about-us/privacy

Overview
Privacy is of great concern to most users of the Internet, and is a critical part of an enjoyable and satisfactory user experience. We at GEOTEC are sensitive to the privacy concerns of our subscribers and other visitors to our Web sites. Whether you are a subscriber or a visitor to our site, we assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us. If you are subscribing to our products, you may be asked to provide certain personal information. Please note, however, that we are asking for this information for the limited purposes of managing your subscription. You should also be assured that we do not provide or sell information about our customers or site visitors to anyone.
Please note that our sites contain links to other sites. GEOTEC is not responsible for the privacy practices, privacy statements, or content regarding these other sites.
Information We Gather from You
Personal Information
We do not collect any personal information from a visitor to our sites unless that visitor explicitly and intentionally provides it. Under no circumstances do we collect any personal data revealing racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religious or philosophical beliefs, trade union membership, health, or sex life. If you are simply browsing our sites, we do not gather any personal information about you.
Subscriptions
If you choose to subscribe to our products or services, we will request certain information from you such as your name, address, and e-mail address information.
Statistical Information about your Visit
When you visit our sites, our computers may automatically collect statistics about your visit. This information does not identify you personally, but rather about your visit to our sites. We may monitor statistics such as how many people visit our sites, the user's IP address, which pages people visit on our sites, from which domains our visitors reach our sites, and which browsers people use. We use these statistics about your visit for aggregation purposes only. These statistics are used to help us improve the performance of our Web sites.
Our Security Procedures
We consider the protection of all personally identifiable information we receive from our Web site visitors and subscribers as critical to our corporate mission. Please be assured that we have security measures in place to protect against the loss and misuse of any information we receive from you. As with any transmission over the Internet, however, there is always some element of risk involved in sending personal information.
Facilitating the Support, Renewal, and Purchase of our Products and Services.
We may use the information you submit to contact you to discuss the support, renewal, and purchase of our products and services. Please be assured that we will keep the communications to a minimum and you will have an option to opt-out or unsubscribe anytime.
Contact Information
Our contact information is available at the Contact us.
Prev
Next
tweet
About GEOTEC Software
GEOTEC Software is providing universities and consulting companies by the right tools for the last 20 years. We also assist our clients on various geostructural projects. From basic to advanced problems, GEOTEC Software can provide you with the right technical assistant.
Latest News
ELPLA, Piled-Raft Foundation Design Software New Edition V11.4
23 April 2019
Hochschule Kaiserslautern, University of Applied Sciences, Has Ordered GEOTEC Office 11.3
12 March 2019
The RheinMain University of Applied Sciences
- Germany, has ordered GEOTEC Office 11.4 Unlimited
12 March 2019
GEOTEC Products
GEOTEC OfficeQuickELPLABOHRELPLA
Language
Search
Search
ELPLAELPLA EditionsNew FeaturesTypical Application & ExamplesTutorial ExamplesVerification ExamplesPractical ExamplesReinforced Concrete Design ExamplesPiled Raft FoundationCalculation MethodsGeometry and LoadsBoundary ConditionsSoilGraphical DrawingDrawing SectionsTabulating Data and ResultDesign of SlabSelf-Adaptive MeshDownloadsAbout UsContact UsAbout UsPrivacyNewsBuy
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website.I accept
